channel3000.com 2010-12-18

# Madison News - Madison WI News, Breaking News And Headlines

**Internet Broadcasting Systems Private Policy:**  
Internet Broadcasting Systems and its affiliates ("IBS") have created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: [www.Channel3000.com](http://www.channel3000.com/). This privacy policy applies only to information collected by or through this website. It does not apply to information obtained by other means.

**Information Collection and Use**  
This website makes use of browser "cookies". Cookies are files written to a user's hard disk and read by the server programs to inform a website if the user has previously visited that site. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site, and for other purposes. We often use outside ad companies to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our website, cookies received with ads are not being collected by us and we do not have access to this information. Cookies can be rejected by you and if so none of the functions listed above will be performed.

**Are you an E-mail Subscriber?**  
If you would like to unsubscribe from an e-mail newsletter or alert click here.  
If you have e-mail subscription questions, try our FAQ page. **Note: Do not use any of the e-mail addresses on this page to unsubscribe. The respondents are not able to process those requests.

We collect information from website visitors who must register for certain services on-line, from users who agree to participate in on-line surveys, from users who wish to make certain on-line information requests from us and from users who wish to participate in on-line contests and promotions sponsored by us. Because participation in these activities is completely voluntary, the user has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The type of information so requested or collected by us includes user contact information (like their name and email address) and user demographic information (like gender or age). Contact information will be used to notify contest winners and award prizes and, in some instances may be shared with the contest or survey sponsor. Anonymous survey information will be used for purposes of reporting survey results and monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users' personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users' personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. The visitor's contact information will be used to contact the visitor when the visitor has expressed interest in being contacted (visitors can opt-out of receiving future mailings by complying with the choice/output requirements noted below). The user demographic information so collected will be used by us to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying content according to their preferences. If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site or to send an e-card through our site, we ask them for the friend's name and email address. IBS will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site or sending an e-card, as the case may be. IBS stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact [security@ibsys.com](mailto:security@ibsys.com) to request the removal of this information from our database. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. We track and record IP addresses that access our site for reporting and profiling purposes only. We also gather anonymous browsing habits of our visitors to better identify content preferences. User demographic information is shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis in a manner which will not personally identify the individual submitting such information. We may also share personally identifiable user information with governmental authorities when legally required to do so, and to cooperate with such authorities investigating claims of illegal activity such as (but not limited to) illegal transfer of copyrighted material, or user website postings or email messages that contain threats of violence. We may also disclose personally identifiable information in other cases where we have reason to believe that disclosure is necessary to enforce compliance with our Terms of Use. Other than these specific exceptions noted, we do not sell, rent or provide access to any data collected about or from our users.

**Third Party Advertising**  
The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visits to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal in-formation), is used to serve ads to you. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to "opt-out", please [click here.](http://www.doubleclick.com/us/about_doubleclick/privacy/)

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp). 

**Linking and Framing**  
This site contains links to other sites. This site is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. Occasionally when linking to another site, you may still see our site's logo or frame. This is to provide you with a seamless experience when visiting our website. In these cases you are no longer on Channel3000.com and are now on a different website whose information collection practices may differ from ours. The privacy policy of the site you are on will govern how information collected from you is used.

**Public Forums**  
This site at some or all times makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. IBS cannot accept any responsibility for ensuring the privacy of information that you choose to disclose in these areas.

**Security**  
This site has reasonable security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please remember that no computer system should be considered safe from intrusion. Email may pass through many computer systems, and should not be considered as a secure means of communication unless encrypted. Even then, information is only as secure as the encryption method. Employees are made aware of security policies and changes via email reminders monthly. Access is limited to a very small number of employees with a defined need and is password protected. In order to provide the best possible security we review our Web security policies every 180 days.

**Children and Privacy**  
This site is generally not targeted to children. If we learn that we have received personally identifiable information from a child under the age of 13, we will take steps to delete such information or to obtain verifiable parental consent.

**Supplemental Information**  
This site may supplement the information that you provide with information that is received from third parties. This information may be received from our partners in sponsored content sections. The type of information that is shared could include user contact information (like name and email address) and user demographic information (like zip code, age or income level). This site will use such information in accordance with this privacy policy. However, when you leave the Channel3000.com website the privacy statement of the other site will apply to use of information by that site. (See "Linking and Framing" above).

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor. You will notice in all free email subscriptions generated from this website there is an unsubscribe link at the bottom of the message. Simply click on this link to go to a page that allows you to unsubscribe from any or all of the lists you are subscribed to. 

In addition to using the unsubscribe page, you can send an email to [security@ibsys.com](mailto:security@ibsys.com).

**Correct/Update**  
If you desire to change or modify information previously provided you may either email [security@ibsys.com](mailto:security@ibsys.com) or send a letter to the Security Administrator at the address below.

**Contacting the Website**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this website, you can contact:

Security Administrator  
Internet Broadcasting Systems  
355 Randolph St.  
Aaint Paul, MN 55102  

 **Changes to This Policy**  
We may make changes to this policy from time to time. We will post changes to this policy here, so be sure to check back periodically. We will generally use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. If, however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify our users via email or by posting a notice on the site for 30 days. 

Last Revised 02/08
